You're a total Yuko-san supporter, aren't you?
Who do you support, Suzuko?
I support Sonneti.
Huh? Sonneta?
It's an early investment.
Huh?
What?
Jump! Jump!
Jump!
Subasa's calling you!
Sonneti, are you dressed as a frog?
Wrong!
It's actually a bear!
I see.
Ready and...
Here we go!
Zero Zero 48!
No, no
No.
What's happening?
No, no
No
Thank you.
Understudy?
Excuse me, understudies are members who take the places of successors assigned to combat duty.
Or am I wrong in assuming that, Tsubasa-san?
Yes, but in AKB's past, understudies were something different.
In the event a successor couldn't appear in a concert, another member or trainee would take her place.
That is what they used to call understudies.
From the trainees?
Concerts on planets with entertainment bands are dangerous.
Because of this, only those who had completed sufficient combat training could appear on stage.
But with the current high demand for entertainment, we cannot maintain this policy.
You want us to become understudies?
We'll take over successors positions at concerts?
I will now announce the members who will become understudies.
Takamina's understudy will be Kanada Shinonomi.
Yeah!
Kojiharu's understudy will be Memori Kishida.
Great!
That's amazing, guys!
Yukarin's understudy will be Megumi Wanaguchi.
Yes!
Oh my god, this is so great!
Finally, Yuko's understudy will be Chiaris Solo.
Yes!
Amazing!
Uh-oh!
You're getting tons of opportunities so quickly!
That's great, Chiaris!
Thank you.
What's the meaning of this?
If you're going in order, the 76th generation trainee should come first.
That's not fair, Tsubasa-san.
Why a 77th generation trainee?
Yeah!
What's that about?
Just like Succession.
The duration of a trainee's enrollment isn't a consideration when selecting understudies.
Unlike Succession, we select understudies based not on the nature of their soul,
but on their current abilities.
If you're not satisfied with the results, practice.
It's the only thing you can do.
You're bringing back trainee understudies, huh?
I'm not surprised the girls are agitated.
Yesterday, Sensei-sensei...
Understudies.
But Sensei, I don't...
Recently, I've noticed Sensei has been expressing wishes more actively than ever before.
Besides, those lyrics...
That one about the number of something?
Yes.
Ever since the 77th generation appeared, it's almost as though Sensei has been composing lyrics in response to them.
Which means...
Uh, trainees who weren't selected to be understudies have to practice on their own, huh?
They told us we could take a break today, but what should we do?
It's stingy of them, isn't it?
I mean, they could've at least let us practice with them in a corner or something.
Geez.
There, there.
Calm down, Yuka.
In that case, let's binge on Snacks!
I couldn't agree more!
Huh?
It's the 76th generation.
It's kind of...
Awful, I hate it!
I hate impolite girls like that!
Okay, let's enjoy our time off, you guys.
Let's play, let's do karaoke, let's party!
Alright!
I want to do karaoke too!
You'll go too, won't you?
I don't think so.
I'm going to rest at the dorm today.
Yeah.
Nagisa-san is a Yuko-san supporter.
This is different!
From our regular lessons!
This is a completely different level!
No, that's not it!
Right before you flows a river, its path is long and winding and it runs...
Stop!
You've got to show more emotion!
Your audience won't get excited if you don't.
When in your life you find a river, hold on until you fulfill all your dreams.
Never lose sight of them, you can do it!
You've passed!
Really?
Yeah!
I'm glad you're my understudy.
What?
The original Takamina-san had more passion and leadership sense than anyone.
You're the captain of the trainees too, aren't you?
Takamina-san!
Also, if you don't pull back on your dancing when you need to, you'll be off-tempo.
Yeah!
That's all for this afternoon.
I'll work you hard again tonight!
Got it!
I'm so hungry!
I wonder what's for lunch today?
Chinchao Rosu?
Thierry!
We're finished!
It's time for lunch!
But...
Thierry, you've got to bulk up or you're never going to make it through the setlist!
You're going to have to eat lots more and strengthen yourselves!
I think so, you've got to have to wait a minute!
No, wait!
No, no, no, no!
No, no!
No!
Strengthen yourself!
Uh, okay.
Oh my gosh.
There are so many bell peppers today.
Thanks for the food.
I must not be good enough to be an ender study yet.
I'm so hungry.
Welcome back.
How was your lesson?
It's even harder than I imagined.
That sounds amazing.
It's so intense.
My hips are coming loose.
Are you okay, Mamori-san?
Chiri-chan, you don't like bell peppers, right?
Uh, yes.
I cut back on the peppers.
Thank you.
Thank you for the food!
Chef Papa, the peppers were good!
Thank you!
Mmm!
Uh, actually, could I get extra peppers, please?
Oh?
Are you challenging yourself?
Here, I'll load it up with tons of peppers!
I need one here!
Bow!
Um!
Hmm?
Huh?
Sexy!
Alright, I'm in perfect form again today!
I want you!
I need you!
I love you!
Okay.
Sexy!
Jenny, what are you doing?
It's not what it looks like.
Sorry. You're working really hard to get closer to Yuko-san, aren't you?
Yeah.
It makes me kind of happy.
Hey, listen.
Congratulations on becoming… an understudy.
I hadn't told you.
Thank you.
Hey, let's look at the Yuko-san notes I wrote until our evening lessons, weren't you?
Yuko-san notes?
Yeah.
My Yuko-san summary notes.
Chiri, isn't there some kind of big secret you're hiding from everyone?
Anything you want to tell us?
What?
Don't play dumb with us.
We just happened to find this.
Ugh!
Chiri, you're the daughter of the Zodiac Corporation CEO.
On top of that…
Ugh!
Those machines…
Your family's company makes the DES machines that attack our concerts.
It's suspicious.
Really suspicious.
Chiri, are you a DES spy?
That's harsh!
How could you choose her of that?
How could I not?
Are you kind?
Look, it's obvious.
Senpai!
What?
What's going on?
Take a look at this article.
Chiri…
Wait!
Ever since…
Ever since we saw that concert together, I've wanted to join Zero Zero.
But no matter how many times I told my father I wanted to audition, he wouldn't let me.
But I just couldn't give it up.
I secretly went to a Zero Zero concert one more time.
There was a DES attack.
The machines used by the DES in the attack were made by my father's company.
That's why I ran away from home when I found out about the audition here.
From everyone else's point of view, I'm the unforgivable daughter of their unforgivable enemy.
But I had to come, even though I knew I didn't belong here.
That's not true!
I want to become a successor with you and stand on this stage together!
I'm sorry.
Will you leave me alone for a while?
Standing in the line right now, you can proceed right.
All eyes are on.
That's impressive!
All these AKP songs!
It's fun to practice singing like this once in a while.
It's not practice!
It's just karaoke!
And I know…
Doing this won't help us become successors.
I actually think practicing will get us there sooner.
But I'm dead fast and I'm drunk.
And I'm drunk from here.
I will not be too long.
Still I'm the only one!
Into me standing!
It's not karaoke!
It's in Kenya!
Okay, good work!
The successors can leave.
I want the trainee understudies to stay here.
Thank you very much!
Chieri didn't know.
Yeah, I wonder what happened.
Ushiyama Sensei…
Excuse me, I'm going to go get Chieri.
Stop!
What?
I understand that you're concerned about your fellow trainee.
That's to be commended.
But right now, you have a role as an understudy,
so you're staying here.
A role, huh?
Chieri abandoned that role.
You don't have the time to worry about her.
Aren't you trying to move upwards right now, Kanara?
Regardless, please let me go.
I may be an understudy, but I'm captain of the trainees first!
I just can't leave her!
Kanata!
What a stubborn young lady.
So, shall we have the two of you practice harder?
You could all use the work!
Yes!
Listen, practicing together made me realize something.
I think Kanata is plenty good enough to become a successor.
She's talented and works hard.
Hmm.
You're right.
But we don't actually have any real idea how they go about choosing successors.
I'm thinking of talking to Tsubasa-san about this.
So she'll finally make Kanata a successor.
That's the spirit, Captain!
You're the only one for me!
I love you!
Kiss, kiss, kiss!
As long as you're already doing it, maybe I'll join in!
So will I then.
Let's bring it on!
What are you killing?
We shouldn't be here.
This is the place they told us never to enter.
What do you want to do, Takamina?
Do you want to stop for today?
Hmm.
Huh?
What?
Hey!
My Yu Yu!
So we entered, but now we're totally lost!
I can't believe there was such a huge space under the stage!
Yeah.
Huh?
Amazing!
Are all these Kiraras?
Huh?
Oh!
The original Yuko Oshima?
I'd recognize her anywhere!
You're right!
What is this?
It's the original Yuko Oshima!
She's so cute!
But why the originals?
Oh!
Well, they reflect our souls.
That's it.
I'm guessing that these Kiraras must be the ones that display images of the original
members that's the succeeded.
Huh?
Interesting.
Eh-
Uh?
Huh?
But that's…
You, Takamina.
Okay.
There aren't any new walkinker a single ogre of meidän
The original Takamina?
Kanara?
What does this mean?
What do you think you're doing?
I'm sorry. I hadn't told you until now.
You didn't answer my question.
I auditioned for Zero Zero without telling anyone about my father's profession.
I have no right to be here.
Your father has nothing to do with this!
My father was killed by the DES when I was a child.
I joined Zero Zero to avenge my father.
Chiedi, do you remember what you said?
I don't know anything.
That's why I need my seniors to keep their act together.
That moment opened my eyes.
I tried to act cool, talking about avenging my father.
But it's not my only reason anymore.
I want more than anything to become a successor.
Kanata-san!
Your father doesn't have anything to do with your desire to make your dream come true, does he?
That's why you hadn't said anything until now.
That's a surprise. You cried just like a little girl, Chiedi.
Honestly, I have my hands full of babysitting Sonata already.
I'm in no place to tell someone not to blame themselves or take everything on alone.
But let's both stop doing that.
Come here.
Look, we have friends now who will share our happiness and sadness, so you don't ever have to cry alone anymore.
I'm sorry for interrupting your make-out session.
You idiot. Don't get the wrong idea.
See what I mean?
What are you doing?
This is a holy place! You can't come in here!
What is this?
The original Takamina turned into Kanata. Why didn't it turn into me?
The Kiriras here are Kiriras of succession.
Kiriras of succession?
When choosing successors, we can only choose members based on external reasons.
But these Kiriras sensed the nature of a person's soul.
That means…
Until a year ago, the Kiriras had chosen you to be Takamina, Minami Takahashi.
But as Kanata grew stronger,
they began to show Kanata's image instead as the soul closest to that of the original Minami Takahashi.
The closest… to Takamina?
The Kiriras of succession have chosen Kanata to be Minami Takahashi.
Once you graduate, Kanata will surely become the next.
Are you telling me that Kanata can't become a successor unless I graduate?
Yes. But this is nothing more than a place where the Kiriras of succession reflect souls.
No one wishes for you to graduate.
But successors aren't chosen just based on their appearance or personality.
You always say it's based on their souls!
Succession isn't determined only by the nature of one's soul.
There's experience, cooperativeness, and timing.
Kanata has simply become closer to Minami Takahashi, but you were still chosen once.
You should fulfill your role as captain with confidence.
It's for the sake of…
Takamina! Takamina!
Girls, don't tell anyone.
There's no way we'd tell anyone about this!
After all, the only Takamina we'll ever need!
Our only captain of Zero-Zero is her and no one else!
Ah!
The life is滅びるよ
The one who is in the middle of the night
The one who is born with joy
To the next generation
The dream is reincarnation
It's Robert Dei Knights
Attach it to date
The dream is reincarnation
If our dream is reincarnated
Think trying to advance
When we come to our dream
All of the 00- Gobierno
Tell the story
Try your time
How many years
Did you log on?
Whether or not
Dancing
Remember
I'd follow Takamina-san anywhere!
All the 77th Generation trainees, you'll be acting as understudies for this concert.
They're attacking our ship!
The Kairos! They're illuminating Kaneda!